Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard
[footsteps thudding]
[Godzilla roaring]
[Mark] Andrew!
Andrew!
[Young Madison] No!
[Footsteps thudding]
No!
[Godzilla bellowing]
[reporter 1 on TV]
Thousands gathered
in the Bay Area last night
to honor the victims
of the 2014 attacks.
Part of a wave
of memorials and protests
demanding that the secretive
monster-hunting coalition
known as Monarch
be held accountable.
[Reporter 2] The recent spike
in mass die-offs
in the world's oceans
could be caused by efforts
to locate and track Godzilla,
who hasn't been seen
in over five years.
Top brass at the mysterious
Monarch organization
will face
another intense grilling
as the government continues
to push for extermination
of the Titans.
And rumors persist
that Monarch may be hiding
even more creatures discovered
since the attacks of 2014.
A historic tragedy
that changed the world
as we know it forever.
The day the world discovered
that monsters are real.
[Upbeat music playing
on earphones]
- [smoke alarm beeping]
- Shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
- Oh...
- [Emma] Maddie?
Good morning!
- Good morning, Mom!
- Oh, God!
- [Madison] Uh...
- [Emma] Okay.
[Alarm continues beeping]
[Madison] I made us breakfast.
- It's, uh...
- [beeping stops]
Eggs, toast,
and what was once bacon.
And which do you recommend?
[Chuckling]
The toast and eggs.
Thank you.
Coffee?
What were you working on?
Um, I was looking at recipes.
For toast?
Dad's been emailing me.
But he looks good.
Healthy.
Have you responded?
Not yet.
Madison, I just don't want to
see you get hurt.
I know.
Especially with everything
that's going on right now.
Mom, I know.
Listen, I know things
haven't been easy for you.
But we're gonna
get through this.
Together.
You sure he's gonna be okay?
He is in the safest place
that he could be right now.
You wanna hear some good news?
I finished it.
Really?
You think it's gonna work?
It's gonna work.
[Rumbling]
[creature screeching]
[faint growl]
It's gonna be okay.
[Mancini on radio]
Doctor Russell,
we need you in Containment.
I'm on my way.
[Birds chirping]
[Emma] What the hell happened?
No idea.
She was sleeping like a baby
until an hour ago,
and then, boom.
Her radiation levels
went through the roof.
Almost like
something triggered it.
[Emma] Thanks, Tim.
I can take it from here.
Why don't you get some rest?
No way.
Sleep or no sleep,
I'm not missing this.
[Camera shutter clicking]
[indistinct chatter]
[man on PA] Containment team,
move into primary position.
[Pulsating]
- [Emma] Sedatives?
- [Mancini] No effect.
This thing wants to be born.
[Man] Emergency protocol
is in effect.
Ten seconds to biocontainment.
Her time has come.
[Pulsating intensifies]
[growling]
Meet Titanus mosura.
Or as we like to call her...
Mothra.
Incredible.
[Automated voice]
Activating containment grid.
[Machinery powering up]
[powering down]
- [automated voice] Warning.
- What's happening?
[Roaring]
[automated voice] Warning.
[Mancini]
Something's really wrong here.
Containment systems
are failing.
Perimeter alarms
are going off,
the whole network's
going insane.
[Emma] What do you mean?
How is that possible?
Emma, I think someone else
is doing this.
[Bellowing]
[rumbling]
[Emma on radio]
Containment team, stand down.
I repeat, stand down.
You are scaring her.
- [Yells]
- [screeches]
[screeching]
[roaring]
[men screaming]
[man screaming]
No!
Doctor Russell, I'm sorry.
But you know the protocols.
We have to terminate!
I'll handle this.
Mom! No!
Madison, stay here.
It's gonna work.
[Automated voice] Stand clear.
[Growling]
It's okay.
[Device pulsing]
Mom!
[Grunts]
Maddie, wait!
- [Beeps]
- Maddie!
Get back in here!
Maddie! Go back!
Mom! Let's go!
Mom!
[Pulsing]
[roaring]
[roaring stops]
[warbling]
Son of a bitch.
It worked.
[Chuckles]
- [explosion]
- [men groan]
[gasps]
- [gunshot]
- [screams]
[Madison whimpering]
Mom?
[Mothra warbling]
[roaring]
What we are witnessing here,
Senators,
is the return of an ancient
and forgotten super species.
Godzilla, the MUTOs, Kong.
We believe that these "Titans"
and others like them
provide an essential balance
to our world.
And while some may
pose a threat,
Monarch is uniquely prepared
to determine
which of these Titans are here
to threaten us
and which of these Titans
are here to protect us.
Thank you for the fifth grade
history lesson, Mr. Coleman.
But we still haven't heard
one good reason
why Monarch shouldn't fall
under military jurisdiction.
Or why these creatures
shouldn't be exterminated.
Monarch was tasked
with finding and destroying
these radioactive monsters.
But you either can't
or won't tell us
how many there are
or why they're showing up.
So, maybe it's time for
the military to put them down.
[Serizawa] Killing them
would be a mistake.
They returned because of us.
It was our atomic testing
that awoke Gojira.
Other creatures like the MUTOs
from strip mining
and seismic surveys.
But these are not monsters.
They are animals
rising to reclaim
a world that was once theirs.
It almost sounds like
you're protecting them,
Doctor Serizawa.
As if you admire them.
I admire all forms of life.
Senators,
if we hope to survive,
we must find ways
to coexist with Titans.
With Gojira.
[Dr. Graham] A sort of
symbiotic relationship,
if you will.
Like the lion and the mouse.
Or the scorpion and the frog.
So you'd want to
make Godzilla our pet?
No.
We will be his.
[Senators laugh]
[cell phone vibrating]
Uh... No. No, actually.
[Chuckles nervously]
That's not what
Doctor Serizawa meant.
[Whispers] We have to go.
No one is implying
that we would be
- Godzilla's or anyone's pet.
- Sam, we have to go.
[Williams] Doctor Serizawa,
Doctor Graham,
this hearing is not adjourned.
Doctor Serizawa,
I hope you understand
the consequences
of walking out that door.
Uh, you know what, Senators,
while I confer
with my colleagues here,
I'm gonna set you up
with a very brief
and pretty fun documentary
on Titan reproduction.
I think this is the one where
the genitals are blurred out.
But if not, you can leave
a comment with my assistant.
[Birds chirping]
[growling]
[camera shutter clicking]
[wolves continue growling]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[Dr. Graham]
The feed cuts out there.
The survivors
haven't been able to give us
much more
than what the footage allows.
Only that Emma and Madison
were the only ones taken.
I'm sorry, Mark.
I should've been there
for her.
Who are they?
We don't know yet.
We believe
they were after this.
You didn't.
[Sam] It's the ORCA.
Uh, that's why we think
they need Emma.
She believed that
if we could somehow replicate
the biosonar the Titans
use to communicate...
I know what the hell it is.
I helped build the prototype.
Who is he?
Uh, Sam Coleman.
I'm the head of technology.
I joined Monarch,
uh, shortly after you left.
I'm a big fan of your wife...
...'s work. And you.
That just came out so weird,
I'm sorry.
Emma and I destroyed
the prototype.
And then Emma decided
to rebuild it.
After San Francisco,
she went home to Boston,
spent years developing it.
She thought it could help...
Would help what? Play God?
[Dr. Graham] No.
Help prevent another attack.
ORCA was a grad school
science project.
It was meant to keep whales
away from the shoreline.
Not so you could talk to your
little creatures out there.
Listen to me, they'll think
it's one of them.
You use the wrong frequency
on one of 'em
and you're
gonna be responsible
for 1,000 San Franciscos.
Which is why we need
to get it back.
Emma always said no one knew
the ORCA better than you.
It shouldn't even exist.
[Sam] That may be, Mark.
But it's fallen
into the wrong hands.
And right now,
the ORCA is the only thing
keeping
Emma and Madison alive.
Mark, we know you're hurting.
But if we find the ORCA,
we'll find your family.
I promise.
[Dr. Graham]
When was the last time
you spoke to Emma?
About three years ago.
After San Francisco,
we went back home to Boston.
Tried to put
the pieces back together.
Emma dealt with it by doubling
down on saving the world
and I started drinking.
I can't tell you
how much I hated myself
for letting Maddie see me
that way.
Uh, you mind
if we cut in here?
It's just,
you're gonna wanna see this.
Emma combined the bioacoustics
of different Titans
to create the ORCA's signal.
A sort of baseline frequency
that all the creatures
respond to.
Attracting them,
repelling them,
even at times
calming them down.
It's pretty remarkable
actually.
[Dr. Graham] The problem is
we don't know
which Titans she combined.
But if you can identify
those frequencies,
we'll be able
to track the ORCA
and find Emma and Madison.
[Mark] Jesus!
How many of these things
are there?
Seventeen and counting
after Gojira.
Seventeen?
Most of them were discovered
in deep hibernation.
While others we've contained
at top secret sites
around the globe.
Cambodia, Mexico,
Skull Island.
We even found one in Wyoming.
They're everywhere.
Why don't you kill 'em?
The government wants to.
But Emma and I believe
some are benevolent.
Don't kid yourself.
[Beeping]
Uh... Hey, look at that.
We're here.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Griffin on radio]
Castle Bravo,
this is Raptor One.
On direct approach.
[Operator] Raptor One,
you are cleared
for assisted descent
to pad four.
[Griffin] Sensors set
for three meters.
Beginning sub-surface descent.
This is new.
Yeah, we call it Castle Bravo.
Our new flagship facility
built to track and study
Godzilla on his own turf.
I thought he was missing.
Well, only if you don't know
where to look.
As you know,
at approximately 0700 hours,
our containment site
in China's Yunnan Rainforest
was raided.
The specimen,
code name Mothra, escaped.
Only to cocoon itself later
under a nearby waterfall.
While Doctor Emma Russell
and her daughter Madison
were taken hostage.
This is the man responsible,
Alan Jonah.
A former British army colonel
turned ecoterrorist.
Obsessed with restoring
natural order.
And to fund his operations,
he began trafficking
in a new and dangerous market.
Titan DNA.
What the hell is someone gonna
do with a giant worm?
[Rick] Are you kidding,
Martinez?
What can't you do with it?
Pharmaceuticals,
bioweapons, food...
Hell, there isn't a country
or a company on the planet
that doesn't wanna get its
hands on one of these suckers.
And remember,
this is just a larva.
That's a baby.
After it cocoons,
something else
is gonna crawl out.
Something bigger, meaner...
- We don't know that, Rick.
- [Rick] Oh, yeah?
Just wait for it, Chen.
Our intel indicates
that Jonah wants
to capture this specimen.
Alive.
Which means that he and his
mercs won't be far behind.
At 0500, we'll ship out
to launch a joint operation...
I wouldn't bother.
Excuse me?
[Mark] Sounds like
a duck hunt to me.
Uh, Mark, why don't we let
Colonel Foster finish...
A decoy. A diversion.
Look, they've already got Emma
and the ORCA.
Why would they want just this
one when they've got the keys
to your entire magic kingdom
of horrors back here?
I think that they want you
to go after this Mothra
so they can go
after a real prize.
Something bigger.
Right.
Mark,
this is not the first specimen
they've captured.
They know what they are doing.
[Mark] That's not
just a specimen.
I've got an ex-wife
and a daughter out there,
in case you forgot.
No. No one has
forgotten that, Mark,
but, uh, to remind you,
you were brought on here
to help track the ORCA,
and to advise us...
I advise you to kill
these things. All of 'em.
Especially him.
You wanna make sure
these things
don't fall
into the wrong hands?
You kill them
and the ORCA's useless.
Emma wouldn't have
wanted that.
Even to save her life.
Well, it wouldn't be
the first time
Emma put all of this
before herself
or her family, would it?
Dude hates Titans.
Yeah, well, you would too,
if you were him.
[Pilot 1] Outpost 32,
this is Raptor Five,
on approach with
reinforcements and supplies.
Requesting permission to land.
Serizawa has all sites
on high alert,
so transmitting
emergency codes now.
[Operator]
Copy that, Raptor Five.
Codes are good.
Nice to have you back.
Go.
It's good to see ya.
- Need a hand with offload?
- No, we're good!
[Man] We're gonna put it
over at bay five.
- Follow me!
- [Woman] Go back up! Hey, hey!
- Leave them, let's go!
- [Gunfire]
[people screaming]
[automatic gunfire continues]
I'm scared.
I know. Me, too.
[Jonah] Okay.
[Breathes deeply] Let's go.
[Wind howling]
Eyes straight ahead.
Deep breaths.
Just like we talked about.
Hmm.
Mother of God.
She had nothing to do
with this.
Monster Zero.
[Jonah] Any survivors?
[Asher] No. They tried to
launch an emergency beacon,
but we cut them off in time.
They'll figure it out.
Fire up the drills.
[Whistles]
[Jonah] Do you have
everything you need?
Good.
Well, let's get started.
[Man] Further.
We have a grizzly situation
up here in the attic.
[Mark] Come on, Andrew.
Andrew.
[Andrew] I've come to eat
your horses.
[Mark] No, you can't eat
my horses...
That's not...
Stop.
Look.
- An intruder! Get her!
- Get her!
- Get her! Get her!
- [Emma] No, don't get me!
[Mark] Andrew, Madison!
Get her!
- [Andrew] Get her!
- [Mark] Bear kisses.
- [Grunting]
- [Emma laughing]
[Mark] Bear kisses!
[Rumbling]
[Foster] All personnel, report
to battle stations. Code red.
All personnel,
report to battle stations.
- Code red.
- At least 60 knots.
This is not a drill.
All personnel,
report to battle stations.
- Code red.
- [Alarm blaring]
What's happening?
Something's wrong.
He's never been
this close before.
- Who's he?
- Who do you think?
[Rumbling]
He's taking out
our observation drones.
Trajectory?
Straight at us!
1,200 meters and closing.
G-Team. Barnes,
Martinez, Hendricks,
I want you on those CROWS now!
You heard boss lady!
Let's move!
[Whirring]
Doctor Stanton.
Do you have his bioacoustics?
Acoustics coming up!
[Beeping]
Okay, he's closing.
We're at 800 meters!
[Dr. Graham]
Its movements are erratic.
Heart and breathing elevated.
[Sam] Yeah, he's definitely
not happy about something.
How are they getting all this?
Emma isolated
Godzilla's bioacoustics.
It allows us to track him.
Even to get his vitals.
[Rumbling]
Circling now,
closing in, 200 meters.
Colonel!
All teams in position,
weapons hot,
ready to engage on my command.
[Weapons powering up]
Come on, come on, come on.
Hold your fire.
We don't know he'll attack.
[Mark] He will if you keep
those guns on him.
Now I want him dead
more than anybody,
but unless this is a fight
that you know that you can win,
for God's sake, stand down.
[Rumbling]
Stand down.
You can't be serious.
I am.
Stand down.
[Foster] Stand down.
I say again,
safe your weapons.
Do not engage.
[Creature's heart
beating steadily]
Listen.
His heart rate, it's slowing.
[Faint growl]
Open the shields.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Let's bring him in for a beer.
You out of your goddamn mind?
Let him know
we're not a threat.
Open the shields.
Do it.
Hey, what's with
the light show?
It's an intimidation display.
Like a gorilla
pounding his chest.
[Sam] Consider us very
intimidated.
I don't think it's for us.
What are you doing, dude?
[Faint bellowing]
[all sigh with relief]
[Sam] Well,
that was interesting.
Jesus!
Can we maybe
close the shield now?
Show me
his territorial routes.
What? Why?
Because I wanna start
a boat tour. Just show me.
- [Rick] Okay. Coming up.
- [Typing]
You care to tell us
what you're looking for?
[Mark] When an animal leaves
its hunting ground,
it's usually because
it's threatened by something.
Run a course projection.
[Mark] We gotta go after him.
He's looking for something
out there.
It could be the ORCA.
Doctor Stanton,
what's your projection?
[Rick] All paths have him
landing in the same place.
Antarctica.
Good, then.
I mean, let's go!
Let's go find him. Let's...
Wait, what's in Antarctica?
[Foster] Barnes,
contact the Argo.
Yes, ma'am.
[Dr. Graham]
The specimen at this site
has been kept
entirely off-book.
And since it's
a more recent discovery,
our data is limited.
But it seems to be
another apex predator.
Emma called it Monster Zero.
[Dr. Graham] It may have been
a rival alpha to Godzilla.
Battling for dominance
over the other Titans.
Doctor Chen?
I've been scouring through
thousands of years
of myths and legends.
But it's almost as if
people were scared
to even write about it.
As if it was meant
to be forgotten.
Sorry, I hate to crash
a party,
but I got some bad news.
You could just say news.
It's always bad.
We lost Godzilla.
He dropped off the scan
near Venezuela.
Dropped off?
I'm telling you,
Doctor Brooks was right.
It's a Hollow Earth.
That's how he moves around
so fast
using these underwater tunnels
like wormholes.
Just zippin' around.
[Foster] Everyone look sharp.
We're approaching the base.
[Beeping]
- They're here.
- Keep 'em busy.
Launch reaction force.
Move out!
[Man] All right, gents!
Got the green light!
[Dr. Graham]
If Jonah is looking
to extract genetic samples
they'll be here
in the bio labs.
[Barnes]
All right, two minutes!
Check your equipment,
stand by the door.
Come on, Ash.
Make it snappy.
- [Asher] Detonator ready.
- Let's go.
Come on, Maddie.
[Asher] Move! Move!
Remember, eyes wide.
We got friendlies in here.
[Barnes on radio]
Move to tunnel two.
Stay on overwatch.
[Soldier] Roger that, Chief.
[Explosion]
[Barnes] Ambush! Ambush!
[Men clamoring]
Team under fire! 360 ambush!
We're taking heavy losses.
Break right!
[Screaming]
[Foster] Hold your fire!
Hold your fire!
We got friendlies!
[Madison] No!
Mark?
Get down there and help
Barnes. I'm going after him.
Roger that.
[Alarm blaring]
Hey, guys.
I'm getting an EKG reading.
Emma?
Maddie!
Number one, let's go.
[Foster]
Barnes, this is Foster.
I've got eyes on the target.
Repeat, eyes on the target.
Let 'em go!
- [Jonah] Ash!
- [Madison] Dad!
- Mark.
- Emma, Madison, let's go.
Dad.
[Mark] Let's go.
- Emma, Maddie, come on.
- [Madison] Daddy?
Madison, walk to me.
Walk to me now.
Come on, honey.
Barnes, I've got two hostages,
one target down.
- Now! Come on, Maddie.
- I do not have a shot.
Repeat, I do not have a shot.
Emma, what are you doing?
Let's go. Come on!
- Dad.
- Maddie.
Dad.
Madison.
[Creature's heart
beating steadily]
[dialogue inaudible]
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
Run.
[Beeps]
[grunting]
[Mark] Maddie!
[Madison] Dad!
Move, move!
[Creature roaring]
- [Martinez] Foster!
- [Soldier] Get out of the way!
- Let's go!
- Hang on! Move!
[Martinez]
Hendricks, on the double!
- I got you, Colonel!
- [Barnes] Get her legs!
We gotta go!
Damn it!
Martinez, Foster, let's go!
Move, move! Come on!
[Man] Come on, let's go!
Strap in!
[Pilot] No checklist this time.
Check clearance right.
[Baker] Clear right.
- What is Dad doing here?
- I don't know, honey.
- [Baker] Let's go.
- [Engine powering up]
We can't leave him.
[Jonah] What are you
waiting for?
Wake it up.
[Soldier] Let's go! Move it!
[Screaming]
[explosion]
[beeping]
[high-pitched pulsing]
[pulsing continues]
[soft growling]
[thunder crashing]
You gotta be fucking kidding.
[Roars]
[Barnes] Fall back! Fall back!
- Get to the chopper!
- [Roaring]
[Martinez] Go, go, go!
[Screaming]
[Monster Zero roaring]
[soldier] Open fire!
[Yells]
[panting]
[alarm blaring]
[Griffin] We'll do an emergency
vertical take-off at max RPM.
Number two's
still speeding up.
[Thunder crashing]
Oh, shit.
[Roars]
[all grunting]
[engine shuts down]
[growls]
[Foster]
This is Raptor One to Argo.
Requesting immediate
urgent extract.
Again, I say urgent extract.
Griffin, get us the hell
out of here!
Madison!
Madison, no!
[High-pitched pulsing]
[screeching]
- You need to let go of it!
- No! No! No!
- [Jonah] Madison!
- [Emma] Maddie! Let go!
[Madison] No!
[Pulsing stops]
[growls softly]
[rumbling]
[all scream]
[Griffin] Argo, this is
Raptor One. We've been hit.
All systems are down.
[Growling]
[Barnes] Look out!
[Chittering]
[hissing]
[pinging steadily]
[pinging intensifies]
[thudding]
[rattling]
[screeching]
[roaring]
Everybody, hold on!
[Godzilla roars]
[Monster Zero shrieks]
[all grunting]
Mark!
[Foster] Everybody,
clear out. Let's go!
[Martinez] Go! Go!
- [Dr. Graham] Mark!
- [Mark] I'm stuck.
[Godzilla screeches]
[roars]
[Dr. Graham] Are you all right?
[Mark] Got it!
I got it. Go, go!
[Monster Zero screeching]
[Godzilla roars]
[pulsating]
[screeches]
[roars]
[people scream]
[screeches]
[screams]
[gasps]
[roars]
[groans]
[Godzilla roars]
[roaring]
[machine beeping]
Anything on the satellites?
Subs have Godzilla hauling ass
off Argentina.
We lost Monster Zero in
a tropical storm over Brazil.
Scanning the entire
Southern Hemisphere.
So far, nothing.
[Foster]
Then scan the Northern.
[Rick] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Foster]
I know what I saw, Sam.
And I'm telling you,
she pulled that trigger.
All due respect, Colonel,
you saw wrong.
Okay? She wouldn't
have done it.
Christ, she recruited pretty
much everyone in this room.
Maybe Jonah forced her, right?
Maybe he used Madison
as leverage.
No, no. It had to be
someone else.
[Mark] Emma.
It was Emma.
Foster saw it right.
It was her.
No one forced her to.
Are you sure?
[Foster]
First, she releases Mothra.
And now Monster Zero.
Anyone else sensing
a pattern here?
[Dr. Chen] Yes,
and not a good one.
It's as if she is trying
to start a mass awakening.
Well, it's just too bad
that no one tried
to warn you that
that was gonna happen.
[Sam] Hang on, guys.
Why the hell would she
want to release them?
And why would she
team up with Jonah,
of all people, to do it?
We'll ask her
when we find her.
So, let's keep looking.
[Foster] Godzilla
appears to be following
the same path
as Emma's osprey,
heading north
over South America to here.
Outpost 56 in Isla de Mara,
Mexico.
We touch down there
in ten minutes.
[Mark] What about the people?
I'm sorry?
The people. The people
down there in that village
that don't realize
they're gonna be
the special of the day.
We've sent G-Team
to begin an evacuation.
[Officer German]
Doctor Serizawa,
we have a call
on the emergency channel
from Isla de Mara.
Answer it.
I suppose I should go first.
Where's Madison?
- She's right here with me.
- Dad, are you okay?
Madison, you all right, hon?
[Madison] Dad...
I'm sorry.
You don't need to be...
[Emma] It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
She's fine, Mark, trust me.
[Foster]
Trust is a little hard
to come by, Doctor Russell.
Especially after
what you pulled.
[Emma] I know.
And I can only imagine
what you're all thinking.
But if there were any other
way to do this, I would.
Do what, Emma?
I'm saving the world.
But by releasing those things?
That doesn't make sense.
As impossible
as it seems, it does.
Hear me out, Mark.
After we lost Andrew,
I swore his death
would not be in vain.
That I would find an answer.
A solution to why
the Titans were rising.
But as I dug deeper,
I realized that
they were here for a reason.
And that despite all the years
that we spent
trying to stop them,
we never dared
to confront the truth.
Which truth?
Humans have been the dominant
species for thousands of years
and look what's happened.
Overpopulation,
pollution, war.
The mass extinction we feared
has already begun.
And we are the cause.
We are the infection.
But like all living organisms,
the earth unleashed a fever
to fight this infection.
Its original
and rightful rulers,
the Titans.
They are part of the earth's
natural defense system.
A way to protect the planet,
to maintain its balance.
But if governments are allowed
to contain them, destroy them,
or use them for war,
the human infection will only
continue to spread.
And within our lifetime,
our planet will perish,
and so will we.
Unless we restore balance.
[Rick] And what's gonna
be left, if you do this?
A dead, charred world,
overrun by monsters?
No, Doctor Stanton,
the exact opposite.
Just like how a forest fire
replenishes the soil
or how a volcano
creates new land,
we have seen signs that these
creatures will do the same.
San Francisco, Las Vegas,
wherever the Titans go,
life follows,
triggered by their radiation.
They are the only thing
that can reverse
the destruction
that we started.
They are the only guarantee
that life will carry on.
But for that to happen,
we must set them free.
You are murdering the world.
[Emma] No.
Because as difficult
as this will be,
I promise
humanity will not go extinct.
Using the ORCA, we will return
to a natural order.
A forgotten order,
where we coexisted
in balance with the Titans.
The first gods.
This is a dangerous path.
You are meddling with forces
beyond our comprehension.
Gambling with
the lives of billions!
And what are you gambling
with, Serizawa?
Monarch is broken.
It's on the verge of being
shut down by a government
whose only objective is to
eradicate the creatures.
And if that happens,
what will our chances be?
You are out
of your goddamn mind!
First, you put
our daughter's life in danger,
and now you get to
decide the fate of the world.
- That's rich, Emma!
- I couldn't be more sane,
and Madison
couldn't be stronger.
After we lost Andrew,
I trained her to survive.
And at least now, she will
have a fighting chance.
A fighting chance? Why don't
you listen to yourself?
It's not all math, Emma.
Some things,
you can't control.
And there are some things
that you can't run from.
This won't bring him
back to us.
I can only urge you all
to take refuge.
Over the last 60 years,
Monarch has prepared bunkers
around the world
to save
and restart civilization.
I suggest you find them.
That bitch.
How long
until this thing lands?
Three minutes.
[Rick] You might
want to rethink that.
[Foster] Why?
Something's not right.
Check this out.
Emma's not at Isla de Mara.
I mean, the signal's too weak
to be local.
She's bouncing it off
our satellites.
They must be holed up
in one of our old bunkers.
She could be anywhere.
- [Alarm beeping]
- What is that?
Oh, Jesus! She shut down
the containment system.
How much time do we have?
Containment system bypassed.
We're patched in.
- [Jonah] Hmm.
- Ready to broadcast the ORCA.
Doctor?
[Madison] Mom, don't!
I'm sorry, did a child
just tell you what to do?
Maybe Dad is right.
Maybe this isn't the way.
By all means, Doctor Russell,
let's reconsider
our entire plan.
Especially after telling
your friends about it.
Madison, we talked about this.
No, you said you were
gonna help people,
that you would let them
find shelter.
We don't have time for this!
Did you really think
this was gonna be easy?
Painless?
Is that what you told her?
Leave her out of this.
Why? You're the one
who pulled her into it.
Madison, tell me, what exactly
did Mommy sell you on?
Some grand utopia?
Man and monster,
living together
- in blissful harmony?
- [Alarm beeps]
[Winston] Sir, they're
attempting to lock us out.
It's now or never.
Emma, you came to me.
This is your plan.
We both want
to save the planet,
but everything is going to die
if we don't see it through.
Please, at least let them
get to safety.
Ma'am, our window's closing.
Mom...
[beeping]
[Emma] I'm sorry, Madison.
This is bigger
than just you and me.
[Beeping]
[device pulsing]
- [siren wailing]
- [people clamoring]
[Barnes] Tell them
to slow it down!
- Tell them to stand back!
- [Man translating]
[people shouting]
- Move! Get out of the way!
- [Woman groans]
[woman speaking Spanish]
- [creature screeching]
- [woman gasps]
[rumbling]
[device pulsing on speakers]
[air hissing]
[all scream]
[creature chittering]
[soldier] Clear, men!
[Creature roaring]
[men grunt]
- [creature roaring]
- [all screaming]
You got a catchy name
for this one?
Local legends call it
Rodan, the fire demon.
- That's comforting.
- [Rodan roaring]
- [rapid beeping]
- [Sam] Guys?
You remember
that tropical storm
where we lost Monster Zero?
It's changing direction
and, uh,
guess where it's headed now.
That's not possible.
No storm moves that fast.
[Dr. Chen] Unless
it's not a storm.
- [Sam] Oh, man!
- [Serizawa] We need time
to finish the evacuation.
[Sam] Well,
then you'd better hurry,
'cause it's closing in fast.
Serizawa,
it's not a coincidence
that Monster Zero thing
is headed here.
It's reacting
to Big Bird's cries.
That means it's coming
for food, a fight, or a...
- [Rodan roaring]
- Something more intimate.
What do you suggest?
[Foster on radio]
All fighters,
weapons free.
[Screeching]
[roaring]
Oh, I think
we got his attention.
[Foster] Everyone strap in.
All ships, follow our lead.
[Growls]
[roaring]
[rumbling]
- [speaking Spanish]
- [Rodan roaring]
- [boy screams]
- [soldier grunting]
[boy] No!
[People screaming]
- [screams]
- Please! Wait!
- It's gonna be okay!
- [Both screaming]
Hang on, kid!
[Man screaming]
[roaring]
Argo to Gold Squadron.
Let's lure this turkey
away from the mainland
straight to Monster Zero.
- ETA two minutes!
- [Beeping]
Gold Squadron,
engage on our six.
[Pilot] Copy. Start the clock.
[Shrieks]
[pilot] Bogey.
Nine o'clock high!
Duster 223.
Get out of there. He's on
your tail! Get out of there!
[Roars]
[rapid beeping]
[Rick] Cobra's Raptor
is off the team!
ETA to Monster Zero,
60 seconds!
[Pilot] Raptor 37.
Bogey coming up on your six.
[Growls]
[pilot]
I'm losing control here.
I'm losing control!
[Screaming]
[rapid beeping]
We lost the squadron!
ETA to Monster Zero,
30 seconds!
[Thunder crashing]
[alarm blaring]
Ten seconds!
[Beeps]
[roars]
Dive! Dive!
[Screeches]
[alarm beeping]
[both roaring]
Jesus,
they're killing each other.
[Barnes] Mayday, mayday!
This is Raptor One to Argo.
Argo, do you read?
[Foster] Copy, Raptor
One. What's your status?
[Barnes] We're screwed,
that's what.
And we got kids on board.
We're gonna need
immediate mid-air retrieval.
Lock on to their position,
and prepare the hangar
for an emergency landing.
Hangar doors are unresponsive.
- Manual override?
- They're stuck!
All right,
which way to the hangar?
I can show you.
Anybody else?
I know the way.
I... Come on!
Hope you got a big wrench.
- [Alarm blaring]
- [all grunt]
[Sam] What's the problem?
Hydraulics systems are jammed!
I'm trying to
jump-start power.
It's not looking good.
[Both chittering]
[screeches]
- [device beeping]
- It's Admiral Stenz.
[Serizawa] Admiral.
[Admiral Stenz] Doctor
Serizawa, Colonel Foster.
I need you and your forces
to immediately disengage
and withdraw
to a safe distance.
Admiral, I don't understand.
We have been developing
a prototype for a new weapon.
An oxygen destroyer.
Designed to exterminate
all life forms
within a two-mile radius.
With any luck,
it will kill these things
and this nightmare
will finally be over.
Admiral, we must
keep our faith in Gojira.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
You had your chance.
The missile is
already on its way.
May God have mercy on us all.
- [Rumbling]
- [beeping]
[Foster]
He's not lying.
It's coming in hot.
[Griffin] Argo, you gotta get
those bay doors open now!
Have the crash
and fire crews ready.
[Alarm blaring]
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
- Look out!
- [All grunting]
[people sobbing]
Hold on!
- Come on, Griff! Come on!
- [All shouting]
- Hit it! Hit it!
- [Grunting]
[yells]
[Barnes] That's what
I'm talking about, Griff!
- [Translator speaks Spanish]
- Everybody okay?
[Zellner] Get over
to the back of the hangar.
We're all gonna head this way.
This way. This way.
Thanks for the lift!
[Monster Zero screeching]
[Barnes] Go! Go!
Oh, God!
[Screeching]
[Godzilla roars]
[screeching]
[rumbling]
[Rick] We're getting
out of here.
The military
launched a weapon.
It's gonna kill 'em both.
Well, that's not
the worst idea.
[Both roaring]
- [beeping]
- [Rick] Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven...
[Godzilla roaring]
...three, two...
[muffled explosion]
[rumbling]
[bell ringing]
[screeching]
[Mark] Jesus.
Doctor Stanton,
can you locate Gojira?
[Static buzzing]
- [muffled pulsating]
- Yeah. I got something.
His vitals are fading.
Radiation levels plummeting.
Come on, big guy. Fight it.
[Flatlining]
He's gone.
Looks like you got
your wish, Mark.
[Screeches]
[roaring]
[high-pitched roaring]
- [screeching echoes]
- [rumbling]
[muffled roaring]
[creature screeching]
[Jonah] I thought we were going
to release them gradually.
One at a time.
I'm not the one doing this.
Long live the king.
[People shouting on monitors]
You're a monster.
[Shouting continues]
[thunder crashes]
[Officer Martin]
Castle Bravo, this is
Containment Team Mosura.
Do you read? Over.
Castle Bravo,
this is Containment Team.
[Dr. Brooks] Anything?
Dr. Brooks.
We've lost contact
with the Argo,
Castle Bravo and the other
containment sites.
Angkor Wat, Skull Island,
Stone Mountain.
All the Titans,
they're escaping.
[Man on radio] Repeat,
this may be our last comm.
[Dr. Brooks] Wait, wait, wait.
It's... It's him.
He's the one doing this.
They're responding
to his call.
[Thunder crashes]
Oh, God!
Where's Doctor Ling?
She's outside.
Doctor Ling! We've lost
contact with Monarch.
Doctor Ling?
[Soft chittering]
[wind whistling]
[chittering continues]
- [electricity crackles]
- [grunts]
[chittering continues]
[screeches]
- [Emma] Madison, wait!
- [Madison] Get away from me!
Look, I know things
haven't gone
exactly according to plan,
but I can fix this.
[Madison] According to plan?
You said that you were
gonna be careful.
That you'd release them
one at a time,
that you would
restore balance!
They were gonna
take over Monarch
and kill the Titans.
I didn't have a choice.
Bullshit!
You said we were
doing this for Andrew.
Do you really think
he would've wanted this?
[Mouthing silently]
[sniffles]
Exactly.
Madison!
[Knocking at door]
[Creature screeching]
[Dr. Chen] Any luck?
No.
Whatever Emma used
to create the ORCA signal,
I've never heard it.
How are you doing?
[Speaking Mandarin]
How's that?
[In English]
"Myth is our compass."
It's something
my mom used to say.
She believed our stories
about monsters and dragons
could help us find the Titans
and restore
our connection to nature.
[Mark] Wait, your mother?
You're second-generation
Monarch?
Third.
It runs in the family.
[Mark] That's incredible.
I don't suppose
your family has any tips
on slaying dragons, do they?
Slaying dragons
is a Western concept.
In the East, they are sacred.
Divine creatures who brought
wisdom, strength,
even redemption.
[Foster]
This oxygen destroyer,
why wasn't
Monster Zero affected?
[Barnes] I mean,
I'm no scientist,
but I think
it has something to do
with his goddamn head
growing back.
Well, I've never seen
anything like it.
It violates everything we know
about the natural order.
Unless he's not
part of the natural order.
What do you mean?
I was able to
piece this together.
[Sam] Well, he looks
vaguely familiar.
[Dr. Chen] It tells
of a great dragon
who fell from the stars.
A Hydra whose storm swallowed
both men and gods alike.
What, you mean an alien?
[Dr. Chen] Yes. He's not
part of our natural order.
And he's not meant to be here.
A false king.
An invasive species.
That could explain how he's
creating these massive storms
and the effect he's having
on the other Titans.
It's almost like
he's reshaping the planet
to his own liking.
These legends,
what did they call him?
Ghidorah.
"The one who is many."
Ghi-what?
She said, "Gonorrhea."
- Huh?
- Ghidorah!
Doctor Serizawa, we're
approaching Castle Bravo,
but there's something
you should see.
[Beeping]
[thunder rumbling]
[Mark] I'm guessing you weren't
expecting these guys.
[Admiral Stenz] Moscow,
London, Washington, D.C.,
all under attack.
On every continent,
the Titans are triggering
earthquakes, wildfires,
tsunamis,
and disasters we don't even
have names for yet.
Now as before,
we have been trying to lure
the creatures
with nuclear materials,
but they are not
taking the bait this time.
Their behavior
has become random.
Erratic.
And with our forces
spread desperately thin
and these things
roaming the globe unimpeded,
we are running out of options
and time.
Excuse me,
do you have something to add?
Yeah. You're wrong.
Their behavior
is not random or erratic.
If I may, sir.
As amazing as this sounds,
they're moving like a pack.
They're hunting.
All packs, from wolves
to killer whales,
they all respond
directly to an alpha.
And this Ghidorah
is the new alpha.
And all the other creatures
are just doing his bidding.
They're an extension of him.
We stop him, we stop them all.
[Foster]
Is there another creature
that might stand
a chance against him?
[Serizawa] No.
Ghidorah and Gojira's rivalry
was ancient and unique.
Right, so we killed
our best shot
at beating this thing?
[Emma] Jonah, you don't get it.
This changes everything.
With Godzilla gone,
Monster Zero
isn't using the Titans
to restore the planet.
He is using them
to destroy it.
This isn't coexistence.
This is extinction.
Listen, while you were
sitting comfortably
in some laboratory,
we've been fighting
for decades
in one dirty war
after another.
I've seen
human nature firsthand
and I'm here to tell you
that it doesn't
get any better.
It just gets worse.
So, I'm sorry
that Monster Zero
isn't exactly
what we were expecting.
But we opened Pandora's Box
and there's no closing it now.
Maybe there is.
[Jonah] Oh, don't be stupid.
You broadcast again,
and you will expose us all.
[Emma] These creatures
communicate like whales, okay?
[On speaker] They can hear
sonar for thousands of miles,
so let's send a team.
Let's broadcast the ORCA
from Fenway.
It's just a few miles
from here.
I could use the stadium
to amplify a signal
that might stop these attacks.
The city's already being
evacuated, so it'll be safe.
[Jonah] And then what?
[Emma] And then I'll figure out
what the hell
Monster Zero really is
and try to stop it.
[Jonah]
Before Monarch finds us?
I'm sure
all your friends will be
very happy to see you again.
[Emma] We can't just sit here.
All right? This isn't
the world that we wanted.
[Jonah] I seem to remember
you telling me
that the world
always belonged to them.
Well, maybe it is time
we gave it back.
[Sam] Mark!
Mark, wait.
What are you doing?
I can't just sit down there.
I gotta do something.
Like what?
- Like go find my daughter.
- How?
Where are you gonna go?
She's the only thing
I got left, Sam.
I wasn't there for her.
I'm not gonna
let that happen again.
Good luck.
[Man speaking indistinctly
on radio]
[soft chittering]
[soft moaning]
[chittering continues]
[screeching]
[chittering]
Beautiful.
[Dr. Chen] Mothra.
Queen of the Monsters.
Are you recording this,
Stanton?
I record everything now.
Everything.
It's like a song.
[Rick] I bet
there's only one thing
that can understand this.
Godzilla.
[Typing]
- [beeping]
- [Rick] Yeah, I got it.
Picking up a reply.
Bringing it up.
[Godzilla roaring]
He's still alive.
So, her and Godzilla,
they're like...
They got a thing going on?
That's kind of
messed up, right?
[Sam] Symbiotic relationships
between two different species
aren't all that uncommon.
Can you track him?
No. Signal's too weak.
But maybe she can.
How many nukes do you have?
Why?
We could help him.
[Foster] This category
six hurricane over D.C.
is where King Ghidorah
is nesting.
Working with all four branches
of the military,
this will be a joint operation
to lure it away
from the mainland,
so that we can continue
evacuations long enough
for our submersible team
to complete its mission.
[Alarm buzzes]
So this plan is what you would
call a "long shot," right?
What do those nerds
think they're gonna do
down there
with a bunch of nukes?
You ain't hear 'em, Griffin?
They wanna bring Godzilla
back from the dead.
[Foster] We'll be out of range
while you're down there,
but a squadron
will stay behind
to keep an eye out for you.
Appreciate it.
[Commander Crane]
All righty, Bowman,
- let's take her down.
- [Alarm blaring]
Dive the ship.
Make depth 150.
Good luck.
Thanks, Sam.
We'll need it.
[Mothra chittering]
[whispers] What time is it?
Time to get a new watch.
Andrew's favorite joke.
You never took that watch
out of your pocket
without him asking
that question.
You told me five years ago,
I'd be trying to save
the thing that took my son,
that would be the only way
to save the family
I have left...
Sometimes,
the only way to heal
our wounds is to make peace
with the demons
who created them.
You really believe that?
Don't you?
Isn't that why you are here?
There are some things beyond
our understanding, Mark.
We must accept them
and learn from them,
because these moments
of crisis
are also potential
moments of faith.
A time
when we either come together
or fall apart.
Nature always has
a way of balancing itself.
The only question is,
what part will we play?
Did you just make that up?
No.
I read it
in a fortune cookie once.
A really long fortune cookie.
[Rumbling]
[Commander Crane]
Status of the ship?
[Bowman]
Some sort of vortex, Captain.
It's dragging us.
1600 feet till impact.
- [Thudding]
- 800 feet.
Emergency blow! 200 feet!
One hundred!
Twenty-five!
Brace for impact!
[Indistinct chatter]
[beeps]
[alarm blaring in distance]
[soldier on radio]
Argo, this is U.S.S. Brody
en route
to evacuation perimeter.
Weapons hot. Ready to engage
Titans on your command.
[Sam] Jesus.
It's like
the whole sky's alive.
[Thunder rumbling]
That's because it is.
Here we go.
- [Alarms blaring]
- Status report.
Can't fix our position.
GPS is down.
But inertial says we're...
600 miles from departure.
That can't be.
I knew it, man!
The vortex was a tunnel
into the Hollow Earth.
It's a subterranean
tunnel system
that connects
the entire planet.
It doesn't matter.
I knew I was right.
- I told you, Chen!
- Shut up, Rick.
One second emergency
blow forward.
[Rumbling]
[Commander Crane] Doctor?
Launch probes.
[Rick] Range 1,000 meters.
Camera good.
Holding range.
Steady.
Jesus.
Pan right.
Looks Egyptian.
Or Roman.
[Rick] No, this is
something different.
This is... This is way older.
Oh, my.
[Dr. Chen] All of the legends,
the stories,
they are true.
They really were
the first gods.
[Rick] If only the earth
and stones could speak,
the stories
they could tell us.
[Serizawa] Doctor Stanton,
any sign of Gojira?
[Rick] Yeah, the probe is
picking up a radioactive blob,
just past that ridge.
Set a course.
[Alarms blaring in distance]
[announcer on speakers]
Attention, please.
Martial law
has now been instated
by order of the President.
The greater Boston area
is now under control
of the U.S. Military.
All citizens to report to
the nearest evacuation center
for immediate transport.
I repeat, all citizens
are to report
to the nearest evacuation...
[reporter on TV] Massive
storms and other disasters
triggered by the Titans
have forced millions
to flee major cities.
And with D.C. hit hard
by a category six hurricane
that has left the capital
completely flooded,
this is the single greatest
disaster in human history.
The grim search continues,
as people around the world
sift through the debris
of leveled homes
in the hope of finding
missing loved ones.
And though this sight
is heartbreaking,
it is unfortunately
nothing unique.
Cities around the globe
have fallen
under the wake
of what many are calling
"The Rise of the Titans."
I think we should stop.
Why?
[Rick] 'Cause I still wanna
have kids one day.
Preferably without flippers.
All stop. Hover the ship.
[Rick] Whoa.
We got O2, CO2, and methane.
It looks like there's some
sort of air pocket in there.
[Whirring]
My God.
Zilla.
- And goodnight, Gracie.
- Pull up the last frame.
- [Rick] Yup.
- [Serizawa] There.
The source of the radiation.
[Dr. Chen] That's why
he returned here.
He's feeding,
regenerating.
This is his home.
This is how
he's survived for so long.
Always adapting, evolving.
It's incredible.
[Rick] So,
dude's got this covered.
Right?
He just needs a little nap.
[Dr. Chen] No.
This process could take years.
We have to proceed as planned.
Hang on.
We're gonna launch
a nuclear torpedo
in order to revive
a giant monster.
Okay, this is...
This is not like
we're just jump-starting
a car.
[Commander Crane]
We have another complication.
Our weapons systems were
damaged during the crash.
We can't launch.
Can it be repaired?
I'm afraid not.
[Dr. Chen] Okay. What if
we go inside, set a timer,
and blow up
the warhead manually?
No way. If the heat doesn't
fry you, the radiation will.
[Dr. Chen sighs]
I'll go.
What the hell does that mean?
There must be another way.
There's no time for debate.
I'll go.
- [Guns firing]
- [creatures roaring]
[roars]
[yelling]
Argo, we are red on ammo
and low on fuel. We can't
take much more of this!
Copy, copy. Just hold them off
as long as you can.
[Sam] Colonel,
take a look at this.
All the Titans have stopped.
[Rumbling]
What the hell
has gotten into them now?
[High-pitched pulsing
through speakers]
[reporter on TV] It does
appear as if the attacks
have ceased
for the time being,
with the creatures going
from destructive to docile
within minutes.
Now, no one is sure
how or why,
but this seems to be
happening simultaneously
around the world.
[Alarm blaring]
What's going on?
The ORCA.
[Emma] What?
I wonder
who could have done this.
Maddie?
Maddie.
[Sighs]
[Rick] First contact,
you're gonna start
losing your long-range vision.
When you surface,
your motor skills
are gonna start to fade,
but I put a helioxed mixture
in the tank,
which should help you
stay stable a little longer.
It was an honor, man.
[Serizawa] Thank you.
My notes.
Are you sure?
He fought for us, died for us.
He's not only proof
that coexistence is possible,
he is the key to it.
Take care of them, Mark.
[Engine powering up]
[sobbing softly]
[Commander Crane]
Bowman, take us out, fast.
[Bowman] Aye, Captain.
- [Commander Crane] He's clear.
- [Pinging]
[alarms blaring]
[rumbling]
[low growling]
[beeps]
[whirring]
[mechanical ticking]
[faint growl]
[ticking continues]
[growls softly]
[speaking Japanese]
[beeps]
[all grunting]
[Dr. Chen groans]
- [Mark] You all right?
- [Exhales]
Bowman, send a distress
message to the Argo.
[Bowman] Aye, Captain.
[Grunts]
[Dr. Chen] See anything?
[Water breaching]
[faint chittering]
Nobody move!
[Sniffing]
[all grunt]
Are you okay?
I know how to find 'em.
[Aircraft approaching]
I know how to find 'em!
Let's make him proud
and not screw this up.
How did he, uh...
By saving us.
Sam, what've we got going on?
[Sam] We think
Emma activated the ORCA
somewhere near Boston.
That's why Ghidorah
and Godzilla
are both headed that way now.
But we haven't been able to
pinpoint the exact location
without the missing piece
of the ORCA signal.
I've got the missing piece.
- [High-pitched pulsating]
- [Sam] It's Godzilla, right?
- I know we already tried.
- It's not Godzilla.
It's us.
[Foster] What do you mean "us"?
Emma combined the bioacoustics
of Godzilla with a human.
That's how she made
the signal for the ORCA.
The creatures just think
it's another apex predator.
[Rick] Well, that makes sense.
I mean, we are a bunch of
horny murderous carnivores.
Yeah, that's real poetic.
Now what?
We track it, we find it,
and we get my daughter back.
What about Moe, Larry,
and Curly over here?
Godzilla will bring balance.
Oh, I get it. A little
Serizawa let-'em-fight action.
I used to love it
when he said that.
No. This time,
we join the fight.
[Indistinct chatter]
What do you think
you're doing?
I don't have time
to argue about this, Jonah.
I'm getting Maddie back.
Not with my men, you're not.
Emma, you said this was about
the greater good.
That the planet deserved
a clean slate.
But now you're prepared
to put all our lives in danger
because your little girl
is missing.
The ORCA is with...
[Jonah] The ORCA
no longer matters.
Man does not control
the laws of nature.
And neither do you.
[Guns cocking]
I already lost one child.
I'm not losing another.
I have to fix this.
Let her go.
We have everything we need.
[High-pitched pulsing
over speakers]
[wind whistling]
[breathing heavily]
[distant rumbling]
[panting]
[Maddie exclaims]
[groans]
[roars]
[high-pitched pulsing
over speakers]
[growls]
[panting]
[feedback whines]
[chittering]
Oh, shit!
[Screaming]
[screams]
[grunts]
[screeching]
[screams]
[groans]
[foosteps thudding]
[roaring]
[roars]
[Sam] Okay, we've zeroed in on
the last ping from the ORCA.
Fenway Park, dead ahead.
We'll lay cover fire
to keep Ghidorah distracted.
[Barnes] Copy that.
Colonel, all squadrons
are locked on target.
For Serizawa.
[Roars]
[snarling]
[roaring]
Is it just me
or has he been working out?
[Rick] Are you kidding me?
Serizawa's got
that lizard juiced!
Damn right.
[Beeping]
[Rick] Oh, boy.
Godzilla's radiation levels
are going through the roof.
We got about 12 minutes
before he goes thermonuclear.
- What do you mean?
- [Rattling]
[Rick] I'm saying
in about 12 minutes,
it's gonna be a bad day
to be a Red Sox fan.
[Rattling]
[Sam] Okay, guys,
you need to find the ORCA,
get Madison,
and get the hell out of there.
Whatever Serizawa did
to Godzilla
worked a little too well.
'Cause he's about to explode
like an atom bomb.
[Barnes] Roger that.
Prepare for landing.
[Barnes] Go, go, go!
- Spread out!
- [Martinez] Flank left!
On me!
[Both screeching]
Madison!
[Martinez] I got something!
Over here.
Come check this out!
Are you all right?
I found the ORCA, sir,
it looks pretty banged up!
No sign of your daughter.
She's not here!
We gotta get out of here!
[Griffin] Let's go!
[All scream]
[high-pitched chittering]
[Mothra screaming]
- [screeches]
- [Godzilla roars]
[sniffs]
- [Mothra screaming]
- [groans]
[Mothra squealing]
[Rodan roaring]
[vehicle approaching]
Get in!
[Rodan roaring]
[Barnes] Incoming!
[All yell]
Get in!
Griffin, you all right?
Martinez, let's get her up.
[Groans]
[engine revs]
- [gasps]
- [brakes screech]
Where's Madison?
I don't know.
I thought she was there!
Well, she's not there!
Take it easy!
- Get that side.
- Okay, okay.
- Look out!
- [Tires screech]
I hope you're as good
at finding her
as you are losing her.
I didn't lose her,
she ran away.
Well, gee, I wonder why!
I can't blame that kid.
If I had these two
for parents,
I'd have run away
from home, too.
[Brakes screech]
What did you just say?
If I had the two of you
for parents,
I'd run away from home, too.
[Both] Home.
[Screeching]
[screaming]
[whimpering]
[Madison screams]
[screaming]
[rumbling]
[loud roaring]
[snarls]
[muffled electric explosions]
[all grunting]
[roaring]
[alarms sounding]
[Rick] Godzilla's radiation's
reaching critical mass.
Six minutes until he blows.
Order all remaining craft
to retreat!
[Roars]
[squealing]
[Rodan screeches]
[roaring]
[groans]
[whimpering]
[pained screeching]
[groans and squeals]
[tires squealing]
- [thunder rumbling]
- Maddie!
Madison!
Maddie!
[Mark] Madison!
Madison!
[Emma] Madison!
Emma!
Maddie!
[Barnes] Martinez!
We got it. On three.
One, two, three...
[all grunting]
[Barnes] Lift together.
[Emma gasping]
[Emma sobbing]
[Emma] Oh, my baby.
Is she breathing?
Mark, is she breathing?
[Mark] Maddie.
[Gasps]
- [coughing]
- Maddie.
Maddie.
[Madison] Mom.
- Dad.
- Shh.
- Mom. Mom.
- We're here.
[Distant roaring]
[groaning]
[screeching]
[groaning weakly]
[Mothra chittering]
[screams]
[roars]
[squealing]
[rumbling]
[roars weakly]
Roger that.
Osprey's coming
in two minutes.
We gotta work fast.
To do what?
You sure about this?
[Mark] It's the only way
to save him.
We fix it, get on the osprey
and draw that thing away
from Godzilla.
Buy him time to get back
on his feet.
[Powering up]
[pained roaring]
Mark, you've seen
what that thing can do.
I know. It'll be tight, but
we have to take that chance.
Are you good to go?
Yes.
All right. One, two,
three.
[Powering up]
That's it.
That's it!
[Aircraft whirring]
Come on, Griff. We got you.
[Mark] Come on, Emma. Let's go.
Okay. Take her. Take her!
I still have to activate it.
[Mark] What?
I'm right behind you. Go!
[Godzilla groaning]
[pained screeching]
[high-pitched pulsing
over speakers]
[shrieks]
[Barnes] Let's go, let's go!
[Madison] Mom!
Mom!
[Dr. Chen] Come on, Maddie!
[Barnes] Go, go, go!
You got any pain anywhere
besides your leg?
[Screeching]
We gotta lift off, now!
[Mark] Wait!
[Powering up]
[Mark] Emma, let's go!
Come on!
Mom!
Mom.
I love you.
No.
- [Shouts] No!
- Emma!
Mom!
[Dialogue inaudible]
[electronic pulsing]
[whimpering]
[snarling]
No.
[Screams]
Mom!
[King Ghidorah screeching]
[growls]
Long live the king.
[Sniffing]
[roaring]
[screeching]
[pulsating]
[King Ghidorah screams]
[screeching]
[pulsating]
[electricity crackling]
[rumbling]
[deep rumbling]
[screeches]
[electricity pulsating]
Jesus.
Good thing he's on our side.
For now.
Look.
[Heavy thudding]
[chittering]
[roars]
[roaring]
[flies buzzing]
It's a brave new world,
my friend.
Such things as this
become much more valuable
since the rise of the king.
My men,
they don't ask for much.
Can't fish here anymore.
Everything's dead.
[Flies buzzing]
We'll take it.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard